youngpeoplefor.org 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy - Young People For

#### Privacy Policy

People for the American Way is committed to protecting the privacy and security of visitors to our websites. Outlined below is our online privacy policy for information collected through this website and email lists. If you have any questions about these policies, we encourage you to talk to us either by:

• emailing us at [membership@pfaw.org](mailto:membership@pfaw.org), or  
• contacting our Membership Department at (202) 467-4999.

###### Resale or disclosure of information to third parties

We do not share or otherwise disclose any personal information, including your name, address, or email addresses with other organizations except where you authorize it (for example, in petitions to elected officials). Only PFAW staff and our authorized agents have access to personally identifiable information provided by visitors to our site. From time to time, we may send you information from other like-minded organizations whose products or services we think subscribers might find interesting, but we do not exchange, trade, rent, or give email lists to third parties.

###### Browser information collected on our website

As with any website operator, PFAW analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of our website. We use an external service to provide real-time reporting to us and our authorized agents of browser accesses to our site, including page views, unique views, unique visitors, repeat visitors, frequency of visits, and peak-volume traffic periods. We do not use this service to gather, request, record, require, collect or track any Internet users’ personally identifying information.

We use cookies on our site to customize the experience of our visitors and to support some necessary functions. We also use cookies to better understand how our visitors use our site. Cookies are not shared or revealed to other sites. We do not look at cookies on your machine for other sites.

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. For more information on how to modify your browser settings to block or filter cookies, see [www.cookiecentral.com/faq/](http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/). However, note that if you reject some or all cookies, your experience at our sites and on other sites throughout the World Wide Web may not be complete. In addition, if you do not allow cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of personalized content delivery offered by other Internet sites or us.

###### Privacy of our email lists

PFAW maintains several email lists to keep PFAW members and policy makers informed about breaking events. Individuals must affirmatively request to join our mailing lists. In addition, we do not share the email addresses on our lists with outside organizations. Only PFAW staff and our authorized agents have access to personally identifiable information provided by visitors to our site.

###### Children’s privacy

Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying FTC regulation establish United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. We do not knowingly collect contact or personal information from children under 13. Our sites are not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13, and we have designed our sites to block our knowing acceptance of information from children under 13 whenever age related information is requested.

It is possible that by fraud or deception by others we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately obtain parental consent or otherwise delete the information from our servers. If you want to notify us of our receipt of information by children under 13, please do so by e-mailing us at [webmaster@pfaw.org](mailto:webmaster@pfaw.org).

###### Security

We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving financial data from our site. In addition, we have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss or misuse of information that we have collected from you at our site.
